cuofco.org 2017-06-06

# FACTS

                                                                                                                     April 2014
FACTS
                      WHAT DOES CREDIT UNION OF COLORADO
                      DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?                 Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                     consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you
                     how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully
                     to understand what we do.
What?                The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                     have with us. This information can include:
                     n Social Security number and income
                     n Account balances and payment history
                     n Credit history and credit scores
                     When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in
                     this notice.
How?                 All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday
                     business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                     members’ personal information; the reasons Credit Union of Colorado chooses to share; and
                     whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                     Does Credit Union                Can you limit
Reasons we can share your personal information
                                                                    of Colorado share?                this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes - such as to
process your transactions, maintain your account(s),
                                                                             Yes                             No
respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report
to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes - to offer our products and
                                                                             Yes                             Yes
services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                           Yes                             Yes
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes -
information about your transactions and experiences                           No                      We don’t share
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes -
information about your creditworthiness                                       No                      We don’t share
For our affiliates to market to you                                           No                      We don’t share
For our nonaffiliates to market to you                                        No                      We don’t share
To Limit our         n     Call 303-832-4816 or toll-free 1-800-444-4816.
Sharing
                     Please note:
                     If you are a new member, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we
                     sent this notice. When you are no longer a member, we can continue to share your information
                     as described in this notice.
                     However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing for our marketing and for joint
                     marketing purposes.
Questions?           Call 303-832-4816 or toll-free 800-444-4816

Page 2
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?     Credit Union of Colorado
What we do
How does Credit Union of Colorado To protect your personal information from unauthorized
protect my personal information?  access and use, we use security measures that comply with
                                  federal law. These measures include computer safeguards
                                  and secured files and buildings.
How does Credit Union of Colorado We collect your personal information, for example, when you
collect my personal information?  n Open an account or apply for a loan
                                  n Pay your bills or use your credit or debit card
                                  n Deposit money
                                  We also collect your personal information from others, such
                                  as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?    Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                  n sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes -
                                       information about your creditworthiness
                                  n affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                  n sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
                                  State laws and individual companies may give you
                                  additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates                        Companies related by common ownership or control. They
                                  can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                  n Credit Union of Colorado does not share with our
                                      affiliates.
Nonaffiliates                     Companies not related by common ownership or control. They
                                  can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                  n Credit Union of Colorado does not share with
                                      nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing                   A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial
                                  companies that together market financial products or
                                  services to you.
                                  n Our joint marketing partners include insurance providers.
